{
    "target_configs": {
        "player": {
            "name": [
                "player_9_GC2NBN",
                "player_12_GC2NBN",
                "player_1_GC2NBN",
                "player_3_GC2NBN"
            ],
            "app_id": [
                9,
                12,
                1,
                3
            ],
            "animation": [
                "crouch",
                "pick_up",
                "liedown",
                "stand"
            ],
            "feature_caption": [
                "A man with medium skin tone, wearing a navy blue polo shirt, black pants, and blue shoes, with a dark watch on his wrist and black hair.",
                "A man wearing a gray suit, dark shirt, and brown shoes with short dark hair.",
                "A man wearing sunglasses, dark green long-sleeve shirt, light cargo pants, black gloves, and brown boots",
                "A woman with medium skin, dark hair in a bun, wearing a dark V-neck shirt, light pants, and brown boots"
            ],
            "start_pos": [
                [
                    -178.877,
                    49.021,
                    98.136,
                    0,
                    87.52956099638624,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    168.203,
                    88.406,
                    98.386,
                    0.0,
                    -90.0,
                    0.0
                ],
                [
                    -251.351,
                    66.54,
                    98.136,
                    0,
                    174.83998659807986,
                    0
                ],
                [
                    69.789,
                    377.271,
                    98.136,
                    0,
                    49.33828304574493,
                    0
                ]
            ],
            "type": [
                "None",
                "None",
                "None",
                "None"
            ]
        }
    },
    "sample_configs": {
        "sample_center": [
            -169.379,
            488.639,
            98.013
        ],
        "sample_radius": 723.5915164916254
    },
    "refer_agents_category": [
        "player"
    ],
    "safe_start": [
        [
            622.823,
            589.181,
            128.363,
            0,
            -146.51043011088956,
            0
        ],
        [
            334.559,
            -553.267,
            180.609,
            0,
            118.71000331265965,
            0
        ],
        [
            -674.77,
            68.315,
            98.136,
            0,
            7.0039686913719885,
            0
        ]
    ],
    "Questions": {
        "relative_distance": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_blue_polo, the_man_in_grey_suit or the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_grey_suit",
                    "B. the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_blue_polo, the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses or the_woman_in_deep_V_top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses",
                    "B. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_grey_suit, the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses or the_woman_in_deep_V_top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses",
                    "B. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses, the_man_in_blue_polo or the_man_in_grey_suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_blue_polo",
                    "B. the_man_in_grey_suit"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_blue_polo"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_man_in_light_pants_and_sunglasses, the_man_in_blue_polo or the_woman_in_deep_V_top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_blue_polo",
                    "B. the_woman_in_deep_V_top"
                ],
                "answer": "A. the_man_in_blue_polo"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Which is closer to the_woman_in_deep_V_top, the_man_in_blue_polo or the_man_in_grey_suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. the_man_in_blue_polo",
                    "B. the_man_in_grey_suit"
                ],
                "answer": "B. the_man_in_grey_suit"
            }
        },
        "counting": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "How many individual humans are depicted in the scene?",
                "answer": "four"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "How many humans are actively in a crouch position?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "How many humans are in a stationary posture, either standing or lying down?",
                "answer": "two"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "How many of the individuals in the scene are men?",
                "answer": "three"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "How many humans in the scene are wearing glasses?",
                "answer": "one"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "How many humans are present who are *not* wearing glasses?",
                "answer": "three"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Among the men in the scene, how many are *not* wearing glasses?",
                "answer": "two"
            }
        },
        "state": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in the navy blue polo shirt?",
                "options": [
                    "A. crouch",
                    "B. stand",
                    "C. pick up",
                    "D. lie down"
                ],
                "answer": "A. crouch"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man in the gray suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. sitting",
                    "B. holding an object",
                    "C. crouch",
                    "D. lie down"
                ],
                "answer": "B. holding an object"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "What's the state of the man wearing sunglasses and light cargo pants?",
                "options": [
                    "A. stand",
                    "B. crouch",
                    "C. holding an object",
                    "D. lie down"
                ],
                "answer": "D. lie down"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "What's the state of the woman with dark hair in a bun?",
                "options": [
                    "A. stand",
                    "B. crouch",
                    "C. pick up",
                    "D. lie down"
                ],
                "answer": "A. stand"
            }
        },
        "relative_location": {
            "Question 1": {
                "question": "Where is the man in grey suit relative to the man in blue polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "A. In front of"
            },
            "Question 2": {
                "question": "Where is the man in light pants and sunglasses relative to the man in blue polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. Behind"
            },
            "Question 3": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in deep V top relative to the man in blue polo?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-left of",
                    "B. To the front-right of",
                    "C. Behind",
                    "D. To the left of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the front-right of"
            },
            "Question 4": {
                "question": "Where is the man in blue polo relative to the man in grey suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the left of"
            },
            "Question 5": {
                "question": "Where is the man in light pants and sunglasses relative to the man in grey suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. To the front-right of",
                    "B. To the back-right of",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the left of"
            },
            "Question 6": {
                "question": "Where is the woman in deep V top relative to the man in grey suit?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. Behind"
            },
            "Question 7": {
                "question": "Where is the man in blue polo relative to the woman in deep V top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. To the back-left of",
                    "C. To the front-right of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "B. To the back-left of"
            },
            "Question 8": {
                "question": "Where is the man in grey suit relative to the woman in deep V top?",
                "options": [
                    "A. In front of",
                    "B. Behind",
                    "C. To the left of",
                    "D. To the right of"
                ],
                "answer": "C. To the left of"
            }
        }
    }
}